Guide to the James Perkins papers,1963-1969.
Perkins, James papers,1963-1969.
- Series IV. 1963-1969
  - Correspondence re Willard Straight Hall occupation and the events of Spring 1969/"Challenge to Governance."
    - Clippings - Maryland., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Clippings - Massachusetts., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Clippings - Michigan., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Clippings - Minnesota., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Clippings - Mississippi., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Clippings - Missouri., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Clippings - New Jersey., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Clippings - New York City., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Clippings - New York State., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Clippings - New York State., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Clippings - North Carolina., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Clippings - Ohio., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Clippings - Oklahoma., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Clippings - Oregon., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Clippings - Pennsylvania., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Clippings - Syracuse., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Clippings - Tennessee., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Clippings - Texas., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Clippings - Vermont., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Clippings - Virginia., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Clippings - Washington D.C., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Clippings - Wisconsin., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Clippings - Wyoming., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Clippings - Unidentified., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 51-52)
    - Miscellaneous Mail re Events of Spring 1969, Including Several Supportive Letters., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 53-56)
    - Miscellaneous Mail re Events of Spring 1969, Including Several Supportive Letters., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 57)
      Senior, John L. (Mrs.); Carter, Lisle C.; Prisamt, George.
    - Miscellaneous Mail re Events of Spring 1969, Including Several Supportive Letters., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous Mail re Events of Spring 1969, Including Several Supportive Letters., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 59)
      Colman, Gould P.; Corson, Dale R.; Purcell, Robert W. James Perkins' Convocation Speech.
    - Miscellaneous Mail re Events of Spring 1969, Including Several Supportive, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 60)
      Letters.
    - Faculty Comments re Events of Spring 1969., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 61)
      Sindler, Allan P.; Kahin, George McT.; Corson, Dale R. Declaration by Cornell University Faculty Members.
    - Faculty Comments re Events of Spring 1969., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 62)
      Guerlac, Henry.
    - Willard Straight Hall Occupation, Alumni Letters., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1-8)
    - Letters Answered by Robert W. Purcell., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Letters Answered by Robert W. Purcell, Form Letter B., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Letters Answered by Robert W. Purcell, Form Letter A., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 11-12)
    - Outside Letters re Willard Straight Hall Occupation, Mostly Supportive., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 13-14)
    - Incidents of April 1969; Black Students and the Occupation of Willard Straight Hall. Muller, Steven; Purcell, Robert W.; Bakken, Douglas; Kennedy, W. Keith; Corson, Dale R.; Sindler, Allan P. Special Trustees Committee; Chronology of events, Willard Straight Hall occupation., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Incidents of April 1969; Black Students and the Occupation of Willard Straight Hall., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      Faculty resolutions; Firearms rules; Chronology of events, Willard Straight Hall occupation, draft.
    - Incidents of April 1969; Black Students and the Occupation of Willard Straight Hall., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      Miller, Robert D.; Kennedy, W. Keith Willard Straight Hall damages.
    - Incidents of April 1969, News Releases and Statements by Administration., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Incidents of April 1969, Miscellaneous Newspaper and Magazine Articles., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Incidents of April 1969, Student Government., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Incidents of December 1968; Black Students and Wait Avenue., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    DuBois, Paul M.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Turner, James E.; Armstrong, Earl M. Afro-American Society; 320 Wait Avenue.
  - Incidents of December 1968; Black Students and Wait Avenue., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    Corson, Dale R.; Stamp, Neal R.; Morse, Chandler; Whitlock, J.H. Afro-American Society.
  - Lafayette Collection., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Club of Albany., 1965-66 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Club of Buffalo., 1963 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Club of Cleveland., 1963 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Clubs of Cleveland, Cincinnati., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Club of Delaware., 1966 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Club of Elmira., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Club of Florida., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Clubs of Hartford, Boston., 1963 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Club of Long Island., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Club of Michigan., 1966 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Clubs of Milwaukee, Minneapolis, Chicago., 1963 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Club of Minneapolis., 1963 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Cornell Club of Philadelphia., 1964-65 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Clubs of Pittsburgh and Philadelphia., 1963-65 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Club of Rochester., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Club of Southern California., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Cornell Club of Washington., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Charter Day. Bishop, Morris G., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Charter Week., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    Marcham, John; Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Bishop, Morris G.; Rockefeller, Margaretta. "Great Problems" Project.
  - Lincoln Center Week, Congratulatory Letters., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Lincoln Center Week Speeches., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Lincoln Center Week, 9 March 1965 Events., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Lincoln Center Week, 12 March 1965 Events., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Lincoln Center Week., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Lincoln Center Week., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 48-49)
    Schuman, William H.; Schubart, Mark.
  - Lincoln Center Week, 11 March 1965 Events., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Lincoln Center Week, 10 March 1965 Events., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1968-69 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    Schmukler, Joan. Committee for Reform in the College of Agriculture.
  - Alumni Affairs. Hall, Jackson O., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Physical Education and Athletics., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Constituent Assembly., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - CURW., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Graduate School., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - K Miscellaneous., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    Knight, John S.
  - Library., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - Medical College., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - Personnel Dept., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - President., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 65)
    Browne, Robert S. Black students.
  - Public Information., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Trustees., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Unions of Cornell University Employees., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    New York State Labor Relations Act.
  - New York State Veterinary College., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Vice President for Public Affairs., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Grohmann, H. Victor.
  - Vice President for Student Affairs., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Vice Provost., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Operating Statements, Presidents Office., 1967-69 (Box 38, Folder 10-11)
  - Foreign Assistance Program., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Institute of International Education., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - United Negro College Fund, Inc., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Trustees Weekend., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Acknowledgement Samples., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - James A. Perkins' Speeches, Writings, Reports, Printed Material.
    - "The University in Transition - The Dynamics of University Growth.", 1965 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - "The University in Transition - The Search for Internal Coherence.", 1965 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - "The University in Transition - Prom Autonomy to Systems.", 1965 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - "The University in Transition." Drafts and Reviews., 1965-66 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - "The University in Transition." Volume., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Talks, Comments, Press Releases., 1965-67 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - "Experimental Mechanics.", n.d. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Report of the President's General Advisory Committee on Foreign Assistance Programs., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - "The Dimensions of the Modern University.", 1963 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Centennial Convocation., 1964 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Address to Trustee-Council Meeting, 8 October 1965, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - "State of the University.", n.d. (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - inauguration., 1963 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - James A. Ferkins Biographical Information., 1968-69 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - "Braindrain.", 1966 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - James Perkins Newspapers Clippings., 1966-69 (Box 38, Folder 32-36)
    - Agricultural Leaders Forum., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - "The Scholar - Modern Style.", 1966 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Short Talks, Addresses, Press Releases, Clippings., 1964-69 (Box 38, Folder 39-40)
    - Statements re Residential Club Fire, 19 April 1967., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Notre Dame Commencement, 2 June 1968., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - "Education and the State.", 1966 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - "The Price of Choice.", 1966 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - "The Liberal Arts and the Academic Community.", 1967 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - "The International Dimension of the University." Japan International Christian University Foundation., n.d. (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - "The Future of the University.", 1969 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - "The New Missions of the Private University.", 1965 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - "Attention Must Be Paid.", 1965 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - "The University Community.", 1965 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Statement on Behalf of the National Assn. of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 30 March 1966., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - "The Black in the White University.", 1968 (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Convocation Speech, 21 April 1969., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Commencement Speech, 12 June 1967., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - "The University and Due Process.", 1967 (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - James Perkins' Addresses and News Releases., 1963-67 (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - James Perkins' Article in Alma Hater., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - James Perkins' Remarks at Bilderberg Conference, 27 April 1968., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - "The University and the New Priorities.", 1968 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - "State of the University.", 1968 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - "No Easy Assignment.", 1967 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - Requests for James Perkins' Speeches., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - Commencement Address, 14 June 1965., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - Tower Club Paper, 14 May 1969., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 64)
    - Alumni Association Remarks., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 65)
    - "The Scholar - Modern Style" revised., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 66)
    - "The New Conditions of Autonomy.", 1964 (Box 38, Folder 67)
    - "The Explosion of Knowledge and University Management.", 1964 (Box 38, Folder 68)
    - Inaugural Address, 4 October 1963., 1963 (Box 38, Folder 69)
    - "The New Venture" and "The Heart of the Matter.", 1964 (Box 38, Folder 70)
    - Freshman Convocation., 1963 (Box 38, Folder 71)
    - "Liberal Learning and the Learning Community.", 1967 (Box 38, Folder 72)
    - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 73)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings re James Perkins' Speeches., 1967-69 (Box 38, Folder 74)
    - Miscellaneous Press Releases., 1964-69 (Box 38, Folder 75)
    - James Perkins' Inauguration Clippings., 1963 (Box 38, Folder 76-77)
    - James Perkins' News Releases., 1963-69 (Box 38, Folder 78-80)
    - James Perkins' Clippings., 1963-69 (Box 38, Folder 81-85)
    - Comments on James Perkins' Speeches., n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - "Education and the State.", 1966 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Regents Advisory Committee on Educational Leadership; the College and University President., 1966 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Commencement Address., 1966 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - "Cornell's Second Century" and "Cornell's Financial Future.", n.d. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Summary of CEEB Speech., 1966 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - The Year in Review., 1965-66 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - "The Integrity of the University.", 1969 (Box 39, Folder S)
    - "On Ideals and Experience.", n.d. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - "The University as Community.", 1967 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - "Foreign Aid and the Brain Drain.", 1966 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - "The New Dimensions of the University.", 1966 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Commencement Address, 12 June 1969., 1969 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Charter Day Convocation., 1965 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - "And Service to Mankind.", 1964 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - "And Service to All Mankind.", n.d. (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Convocation in New York City, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      9 March 1968, "The Restless Decade."
    - "Education Revolution.", 1968 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Cayuga Heights School Commencement., 1966 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - International Conference on the World Crisis in Education., 1967 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Clippings and Miscellaneous Printed Material., 1963-69 (Box 39, Folder 21-22)
  - Tom Tobin., 1964-67 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Report of the President., 1964-65 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Report of the President., 1965-66 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Report of the President., 1966-67 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Report of the President., 1967 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Report of the President., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report to the President of the Office of Admissions., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report for the New York State College of Agriculture and the Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Stations., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report of the Dept. of Aerospace Studies., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Annual Report, Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report of the College of Architecture, Art, and Planning., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Report of the Dean, College of Arts and Sciences., 1967-68i (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Annual Report of the Director of the Budget., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report of the Vice President, Business Depts., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Report of the Dean of the Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Annual Report of the Division of Biological Sciences., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report of the Controller., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report, College of Engineering., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report of the Cornell Center for Research in Education., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report of the Dean of the University Faculty., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report of the Graduate School., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Annual Report of University Health Services., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Director's Report, Society for the Humanities., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Annual Report of the School of Hotel Administration., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Report of the Sixty-Eighth Year of the New York State College of Home Economics., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - ILR Highlights: A Report to the President., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Annual Report, International Studies at Cornell., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Highlights of the Annual Report of the Cornell Law School., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Annual Report of the University Libraries., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Report of the Medical College., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Annual Report of the Dept. of Military Science., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Report of the School of Nursing., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Annual Report of the Graduate School of Nutrition., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Annual Report, Andrew Dickson White Professors at Large., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Annual Report of the Vice President for Public Affairs., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Annual Report of the Vice President for Planning., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - Annual Report of the Office of Institutional Studies., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Annual Report of the Registrar., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Annual Report of the Cornell Plantations., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Annual Report, Office of Information Systems., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - President's Report., 1966-67 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - Annual Report of the Office of Regional Resources and Development., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - Annual Report of the Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - Annual Report of the Secretary of the Corporation., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - Progress Report, Six Year Ph.D. Program., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - Annual Report, Vice President for Student Affairs., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - Annual Report of the Director of the Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - Annual Treasurer's Report., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - Annual Report of the Division of Unclassified Students*, 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 71)
  - Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College., 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 72-74)
  - Special Report of the Status, Prospects, and Needs of the College of Arts and Sciences., 1965 (Box 39, Folder 75-77)
  - Report of the Director of the University Libraries., 1966-67 (Box 39, Folder 78)
  - Report of the Law School., 1965-66 (Box 39, Folder 79)
  - Report of the Graduate School., 1966-67 (Box 39, Folder 80)
  - Annual Report of the New York State College of Home Economics., 1966-67 (Box 39, Folder 81)
  - Annual Report of the Graduate School of Nutrition., 1965-66 (Box 39, Folder 82)
  - Annual Report of the Vice President for Student Affairs., 1965-66 (Box 39, Folder 83)
  - Annual Report, School of Hotel Administration., 1965-66 (Box 39, Folder 84)
  - Annual Report, Division of Unclassified Students., 1965-66 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Report of University Health Services., 1965-66 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, Law School., 1965-66 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, Business Depts., 1966-67 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report of the Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences., 1966-67 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, Division of Unclassified Students., 1966-67 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, University Health Services., 1965-66 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - ILR Highlights., 1966-67 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Physics., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Home Economics., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Report to the President, New York State Veterinary College., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Report of the New York State College of Agriculture and the Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Stations., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report to the President, College of Engineering., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Report to the President, Graduate School., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, Finance and Business Office., 1964 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Memorandum, Machine Records Division., 1964 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - President's Report, Cornell University Glee Club., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, Personnel and Safety., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, Cornell Social Science Research Center., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report to the President, Graduate School of Nutrition., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, Center for International Studies., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Psychology., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Romance Studies., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Russian Literature., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Sociology., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Speech and Drama., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Zoology., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs., 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Corrections, Annual Report, New York State College of Home Economics., 1965 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, University Counsel and Secretary of the Corporation., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Report of the Dean of Admissions and Financial Aid., 1962-63 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report, International Population Program., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Anthropology., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Asian Studies., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Astronomy., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Chemistry., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Annual Report, Classics Dept., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Economics., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of English., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Geology., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of German Literature., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Government., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of History., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Annual Report, History of Art., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Annual Report of the interdepartmental Committee on Literature., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Mathematics., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Annual Report, Division of Modern Languages., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Music., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Philosophy., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - WHCU Program Report., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Annual Report, Registrar., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Annual Report, Registrar., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Annual Report, Controller's Office., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Report of Operations, University Auditor., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Annual Report, Campus Store., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Annual Report, Cornell University New York Hospital School of Nursing., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Annual Report, Dept. of Housing and Dining Services., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Annual Report, Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Annual Report, University Printer., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - President's Report, Drafts and Corrections., 1964-65 (Box 40, Folder 61)
    Bishop, Morris G.
  - Annual Report, Vice President for Academic Affairs., 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Annual Reports, Miscellaneous., 1962-64 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Annual Report, University Health Services., 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School., 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Annual Report, New York State College of Agriculture., 1962-63 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Annual Report, Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies., 1962-63 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Annual Report, School of Education., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Annual Report, Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 69)